http://www.chenalinsurance.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
501-221-212814309 Cantrell Rd Ste 5Little Rock, AR 72223 Toggle navigation
HomeInsuranceClaims & ServiceBlogAboutContactPrivacy Policy Chenal InsuranceWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you fill out a form. You may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to the request you submitted online.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or one of our blogs. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us. Get a QuoteGive us some info and we'll get quotes from multiple companies.Get a Quote
Toggle Dropdown AutoHomeownerLifeMotorcycleBusinessMore…Insurance Partners
From Our Blog Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020
Connect Online Chenal Insurance is an independent insurance agency located in Little Rock, Arkansas. Give us a call, stop by, or request a quote online to find out how much we can save you on your insurance.HomeAboutContactSitemapRecent Articles Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020 Quick LinksAbout UsContact UsService CenterInsurance ProductsGet an Insurance QuoteCompanies We RepresentStaff DirectoryContact Us 14309 Cantrell Rd Ste 5Little Rock, AR 72223 P.O. Box 22667Little Rock, AR 72221-2667 501-221-2128 501-221-9874 info [at] chenalinsurance [dot] com info [at] chenalinsurance [dot] com Mon-Thu 8:30am-4:30pmFri: 8:30am - 3pm © 2020 Chenal Insurance | Privacy | Disclaimer | Website by BT
